Hi, this is me. In this video, I decided
to wake up at 5:00 a.m. every day for a
week to see how my body and routine
would react to the Pinterest morning
lifestyle. I hope you guys enjoy and
let's see if I survive.
No, I'm actually falling back asleep.
Okay, good morning everyone. It is 5:00
a.m. I don't know what I'm doing.
You know, I wanted to try out the
lifestyle of waking up at 5:00 a.m.
being productive. You know the drill. I
want to see
I want to see if I'm built for this
life, you know, and this video is going
to be my way of testing it. Hi everyone.
Welcome. Welcome back to my channel.
This video is going to be waking up at
5:00 a.m. for a week.
Wrap it up. That was my you need to wake
up alarm just in case, you know, the
five one didn't work. Yeah, I'm going to
be waking up at 5:00 a.m. for the rest
of this week. This school week, by the
way. I don't know how I'm going to
handle it with school. This is really me
just doing an experiment. So, yeah,
let's get going. I'm so tired.
[Music]
Okay, you guys, I haven't been talking
much because, you know, I'm trying to
like allot myself time to do things
because I don't know how the timing is
going to work since I'm going to the gym
this early. I think what I'm going to
have to do is like prep a little free
gym snack the night before. I'm scared
to open the garage.
[Music]
Okay.
I've never had to drive this early, so I
don't know how this is going to go. The
only way that I'm going to get through
this because I'm actually I'm actively
not very awake right now. If I just play
some
Ooh, I just realized my car is probably
You can definitely hear my car inside
the house. I cannot keep wasting time. I
want to get a good lift in. Made it. I
don't think I've Hello. I'm right here.
I've never driven at the at the I've
never driven at that time ever. It was
so weird. Kind of scary honestly because
I couldn't see my surroundings. It's a
whole different experience and that's
why I wanted to document this week. Like
I just I know this week is going to be
so many different experiences. Last year
and the year before that, I could have
woken up at 5:00 a.m. for a week and it
wouldn't have been that impactful
because I didn't have a car to like go
to the gym. The only thing I'd be able
to do is run in the morning, which, you
know, I've done that in the past. She's
she's fun, but it's really painful after
a while. Hopefully, this is going to be
therapeutic. If it's not, I'm I'm
wasting my time. Speaking of wasting my
time, let's go inside. Today is push
day. So, chest, shoulders, and try, aka
my least favorite day, which I know is a
pretty controversial topic because
everybody loves push day for some
reason. I'm not a push kind of person.
[Music]
I need to see this every morning. This
is definitely a reason to wake up. Holy.
I am done with the gym for today. That
was nice. It was nice not having as many
people there. Actually, I don't even
think it was like not having as many
people. I think it was just not having
people my age. Good lift. I want to go
home now, eat some food. I see a school
bus, but time is currently 7:09 a.m. I
feel a little tired, but I feel like I
still get to have my energy drink today.
I still need to eat as well. So, I think
I'm going to try and update you guys
like every period during the school day
to tell you how I'm feeling. But, I
definitely think that later in the week,
like probably, well, today is already
Tuesday, so I feel like I feel like
Thursday and Friday, I'm going to be
really tired. Tomorrow, which is
Wednesday, I feel like it won't be that
bad cuz I'm still going to have like the
the adrenaline of just waking up early.
But, I can't believe I've been up for 2
hours already.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Y'all, I'm I'm feeling it. I'm not
>> Oh, this is nice. Okay, we're in. We're
in AP Lang. I haven't updated you guys
in a while, but I'm feeling it right
now. So, I think it's time for me to
open this.
>> Yeah. Or anything like I'm going to
actually update you guys from now on.
Also, in my second period, I was
freezing. It was a whole 2° in there. My
body Uhuh. Hopefully, this wakes me up a
little bit cuz I was in math like
genuinely falling asleep. I'm not that
tired right now.
>> I kind of feel
Well, I'm not that tired thankfully.
It's cuz I'm eating.
>> Oh, honey. better tires.
>> I know we see a common theme here.
>> Consistency is key, right?
>> V8 rice and chicken.
>> See y'all?
>> I don't know. Hannah, what's your pulse?
>> Literally 68
>> and it's been stuck at 68
>> for like 5 minutes now.
>> Yeah, I don't. Okay, I think you have a
defective one. Okay, guys. We're in
anatomy.
>> We just did a little stress lab. We had
like
>> stabbing ourselves to cause stress.
>> We're using clothes spins. Probably
pinch ourselves. Stress lab
>> and we're using um pulse monitors.
Basically, we had to like lay down on
these tables and check our resting rate
and then we stood up. We just, you know,
>> it was fun. All right, I am done with
school. I'm honestly done with today.
I'm tired, but I got to go home. I have
to read for AP Lang, study for AP Gov,
and study for honors camp. It's okay.
Overall, I felt more awake today than I
would normally be if I like woke up late
on accident. There's a very clear
difference. I'm going to try and get out
of this parking lot. It's not going to
be fun, but I'm going to go home now.
Maybe I'll tan when I get home. It's
really nice outside. But it has been an
insane past few hours. I've been
switching between studying, finishing up
homework, editing a video, talking with
a few friends. I showered as well. I'm
very proud of the work I've gotten done.
Time is currently 9:59. I definitely
need to go to bed soon because it's I'm
just being realistic. It's not Hello.
I'm just going to be realistic. It's not
sustainable for me to be going to bed
honestly later than like 9:30 if I'm
going to be waking up at 5:00. Tonight
is just a little bit different cuz I do
have two tests tomorrow. So, you know, I
promise y'all I will go to bed soon.
Like I said, I am very proud of my work.
Got my chem here. Go. It's honestly just
chem and gov scattered everywhere. At
some point, I'm just going to put this
stuff away, call it a night, and then we
can hope for the best for tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm gonna finish this up and I
will see you guys bright and early, I
guess, dark and early tomorrow morning
at 5:00 a.m.
[Applause]
[Music]
Okay, today I'm a little more
disoriented. I will say that when that
alarm woke me up, I it definitely wasn't
that difficult like to get up, but there
was this feeling inside my body that was
like, "Hey, just don't get up." Like,
it's never that serious. But today, I
want to try and be more efficient with
my time. Yesterday, I took a long time
to get out of the house. I want today to
be more efficient than yesterday. Also
in the gym, too, because yesterday I was
kind of messing around for a little bit.
So, yeah, I'm going to go get ready, be
quick, and let's go to the gym. I beat
my other alarm.
Okay, let's go. You know, it's crazy
when I'm leaving before my dad leaves
for work. He leaves early. I think he's
leaving a little bit later today cuz he
just got back from a trip. But pre gym
snack today is a banana and yogurt. If
y'all have any suggestions on what I
should eat for the gym, please let me
know. Something quick and easy. I am
leaving the house a little bit quicker
than I did yesterday. I think it's like
7 8 minutes quicker. That's a big
difference when you're in a time slot
like this. So, I made it. That man is
watching me. Okay, I'm not going to talk
much cuz I want to go lift. Today is
pull day. Back in by kind of cold. I've
had the heat on the entire car ride. I
really just want to sit in my car and
watch TikTok. Like, I'm stuck between
doing that and lifting. So,
Another
[Music]
early morning. I am rewarded with this.
I actually This makes it all worth it.
Like actually this is crazy. So pretty.
Wow. Okay. Wo, that was kind of a mid
lift. You know what happens sometimes?
Some effort is better than none. I also
noticed that I was yawning a lot when I
was lifting today, which doesn't really
happen. I definitely will go to bed
early tonight. I think my brain just
feels a little foggy right now as well.
I've been up for almost 2 hours now. So,
I'm going to go home, make breakfast, do
a little refresh, get dressed for the
day, and I'm actually going to get to
the school early. It's literally It's
6:49. It feels like I've been awake for
like 5 hours already. Let's drive home.
Okay, guys. Here is the outfit of the
day. I have two of my favorite necklaces
on. Gray zip up, this Orlando shirt, and
I have these blue jeans, my Tims. I need
to go. Let's go to school. Okay, we're
studying for Gov and Chem.
>> So, the consensus was we don't need to
study for Gov. Um, you know what? I
don't have time for reading that book
for Elang
>> or finishing the TED talk paper.
>> I already have like more than half of it
done. I can probably fidget Fidget
finish. But if she just gives us this
and tells us to fill it in, I can get so
many good points.
>> And this this is pretty easy cuz it's
like whatever it's now this
>> I don't know and I don't care.
Okay, time is currently 8:51. I have a
reason as to why I did not film for like
the past 9 hours. My mood today was very
up and down and I was just like swinging
in and out of like I feel like I can't
do this. I'm so tired. You know, I've
been pretty vulnerable today. I don't
even know how to describe it. Usually I
don't like filming when I'm like that
because it's not not fun to watch and
it's not fun to edit either cuz I end up
literally just making fun of myself the
entire time. I don't know what it was
because I'm really I'm doing things that
like should make me feel good. I'm
waking up early. I'm getting my work
done. I'm being productive. But
something today I think it could have
just been like a normal mood swing. But
I just wanted to document that because I
haven't filmed in forever. But like I
said, it is 8:52. I am about to go to
bed so I can get a full night's rest
tonight. I am also going to finish the
episode that I didn't finish from
earlier this morning at the gym of the
summer turn pretty. I am really really
excited to finish it. Also, I don't know
if I've talked about it yet, but peep my
sleep shirt for this week. It says mom's
favorite. If my sister's watching this,
well, she knows the truth. So,
good morning. I definitely feel it
today. I My prediction found out to be
true. Even though I got a full sleep,
I'm like
I've also been trying different
lightings in the morning to see like if
I'll wake up easier. Different lighting,
you know? I'm definitely awake. My body
is definitely feeling it. The good thing
is though, I get to go hit legs at the
gym today. So, and I'm almost done with
the week. All I'm thinking about is
Saturday because
the state I'm going to be left in on
Saturday, I'm going to be slumped. I
kind of want this 5:00 a.m. thing to be
a normal part of my day. Cuz being able
to go to the gym early in the morning
helps so much cuz I don't have to get
home from school already tired and then
have to motivate myself to go to the gym
cuz that takes so much more time than it
does to just go to the gym in the
morning. It also restricts me from
taking too much time at the gym and just
doom scrolling in between sets. So, I've
also noticed that this has taken me off
my phone from in the morning. I will say
though, this morning before my alarm
went off, my body was already up like 5
minutes before and I went on my phone.
I'm going to try not to do that tomorrow
if I wake up early again. But let's go
get ready for the day.
[Music]
I'm so ready to hit legs today. I'm
going to eat the same thing as
yesterday. Yogurt and a banana. Like I
said, help a boy out. Time is currently
5:48. We're doing good on time. Kind of
isish. I feel a little sicked.
[Music]
I kind of feel a little sick today. I
mean, I felt kind of sick this whole
week. You know, we pushed through.
[Music]
It is an ugly gray blue morning. This is
sad. I am at school a little bit early
cuz I have a meeting with class office,
which if y'all are new here, I'm
involved in a lot of things. I'm
involved in class office, which is like
the elected one where people choose like
president, vice president, treasurer,
secretary, historian, the grade votes.
I'm the treasurer for the class of 2027.
Junior class officers have to basically
set up prom. Like we plan it all and
then we get to go to our own dance. So,
I got to go to that meeting and then
after school, I've got stuff to deal
with school volleyball and then I might
be going to an away game for girls
volleyball. We'll see. Honestly, I'm
doing pretty good for it being 7:41.
I've already been up for 2 hours and 40
minutes. I'm doing pretty good. I'm
going to go inside, get this meeting
done. I really just don't want to deal
with school today. I'm I'm I'm kind of
checked out for this week. Okay.
>> I don't know.
>> Hi guys.
>> We're going to our favorite teacher.
>> New fall drink unlocked.
>> Is it good?
>> Oh my god.
>> It's a iced pecan oat milk latte or
something like that. Holy crap.
>> But it's only 48 weeks, so we only have
tomorrow.
>> I have an assessment in chem, a quiz in
math. Thank you.
>> And then it's like a state pretest for
gov. It's not fun. It's going to be easy
though. Tried it, guys. It was It was
decent.
>> It's really good.
>> Okay.
>> We are in AP. Kenley really wants to
tell me about how she interpreted the
book, but I don't care.
>> She's mad that I don't have food for
her.
>> Okay, update. I'm not that tired. Low
key. I'm chilling today. Student
council. We're walking out to the
football field to figure out homecoming
decoration plans. You know, I also want
to note like I said I'm not tired, but
also today is moving so slow. I feel
like I'm losing my mind and that I've
been at school for like 10 hours when
it's been like 3. Reese, how's your day
been?
>> Um, my day has been really good.
>> Um, go around minus the fact that I have
really bad allergies right now.
>> Me too. Say it again.
>> Hola.
[Music]
Um, we're at lunch right now, guys.
Parade is coming together.
>> Guess that exact same thing in the last.
>> Did we?
>> Um, it wasn't coming together then. We
lied. It's actually coming together now.
We should be done by next week.
>> Bash check.
>> He's doing I wake up at 5:00 a.m. every
day this week.
>> Mukbang. Mukbang.
And it's like the voices. Hi mom. I'm in
anatomy right now. I just finished
everything for the day in anatomy.
>> Is it just
>> finish?
>> We're in Zoom council right now. We're
about to count these cups. We're not
going to count them. We're going to
estimate.
>> I'm just here for support.
>> Keep that.
>> Freaking struggling.
>> We have wax tape. And then
>> this is the speech and debate room.
>> Yeah,
>> that is that makes a lot of sense.
>> We have Mike Chem homework. And then we
have decorations. And then the cups that
we're counting. Wait, how do I flip it?
>> So like Yeah.
>> So you can see it.
>> Oh hi guys.
>> Are actually what it means? Like were
these what the cups came in? Cuz this is
like
>> guys.
>> We're in AP site. We're working on
positive reinforcement, negative
reinforcement, positive punishment, and
negative punishment. It's a little
confusing. She's already taken a site
class, so I don't want to hear it. way.
Punishment obviously in a bad way.
>> Maybe my brain is just foggy. Wow.
>> Like 15 questions and I don't want to do
it.
>> Me and Evan just got out of the girls
volleyball game. We also had one of our
like open gym fall practice type things.
But yeah, the girls they won in three
sets. Clean sweep. And the our student
section was hype as always. I'm telling
y'all we have a good volleyball program.
I don't have a voice again. So, if you
if you watch the what it's like being a
junior, you know I lose my voice when I
go to games. We're going to go home. I'm
tired. We're playing through the
facility.
>> Yeah. I want to play Roblox still when I
go home.
[Music]
I'm really tired this morning if you
couldn't tell by the fact that I needed
to use the late alarm, but that's why
it's there. I'm still up. I'm ready for
the day to be over. That's so bad. No,
today's going to be good. It's Friday. I
only have one test.
>> Finally.
>> I feel like every day has been multiple
quizzes and tests. I didn't film at the
end of yesterday. I if you've seen the
September reset, you've already seen
this. But this is my motivation to get
out of bed. I don't know if the camera's
going to pick it up. I got a media
console. And now my bedside table is my
bookshelf. Okay, but now I'm going to go
get ready for the day. I am too tired
for this. Okay, you guys. I am a little
later than usual on time, but it's okay
because today is only cardio. I don't
think I can physically or mentally have
the ability to hit abs this early in the
morning. I I'll do cardio just to keep
my my gym quota for the week. I used all
of my mental strength for tests I had
this week and waking up this early. It's
really cold outside today. You might
say, "Well, wear a hoodie." I don't want
to wear a hoodie for cardio. I don't
want to feel sweat. I actually don't
want to get out of the car cuz it's so
warm and so perfect. And I know gym is
going to be a little bit colder cuz I
can't. Obviously, you don't want a hot
gym. I'm just thinking about 45 minutes
of cardio.
No, it's okay. I'm going to motivate
myself and I'm going to push through.
It'll be worth it in the end. I'm going
to like the result. I'm going to be
happier. I'm going to be more awake.
[Music]
>> Y'all, I couldn't do it. I only did 30
minutes, but I gave myself a little pat
on the back because this was something
new this week. And 30 minutes is still
better than nothing. Honestly, 30 is 30
is usually like what people do. Um, I
just like to do 45, you know, to go that
little extra that little extra bit. I'm
doing really good on time now. So, I
don't really know what I'm going to do.
It is Friday and I know I'm getting
seven brew after school. No, come back.
Okay. I was just proud of myself because
I was like, I'm on the stairm at like 5
and 6:00 in the morning. Like, just be
proud of yourself. Okay, you guys ignore
that I'm wearing this jacket again cuz
it's a jacket. But my outfit of the day
is really cute. So, I want to show you
guys.
I also only have this jacket because I
feel really really cold right now and
then after school it'll be really hot.
That's just how it's been. It's like
those mornings where it's really cold
and then the afternoon is really hot. So
>> we're trying her sparkling.
>> You know how I have the Yerma mate. So
they have a sparkling.
>> This is the new hoodie.
>> I like it.
>> Wait.
>> That's vomit in my mouth.
That tastes like drywall.
>> Playing music in the hallways always cuz
it's Friday. We just came from Chem. I
literally was like falling asleep the
entire time we were doing the
assignment. I finished the homework very
quickly. We're in math right now.
>> Good for you. Not me.
>> Also got 100 quiz.
>> Guess what class we're in.
I don't know why we're still whispering
because everyone's done with the test by
the look of this
special AP. I am losing my mind today.
I'm so tired. I want to go home. And
Alicia over here is like the queen of
busy work. She'll get it done. I cannot
do busy work at all. But today isn't
even busy work. We're doing our first
FRQ.
I don't want to do this FRQ. It's about
nature versus nurture. So, it's not that
bad, but
>> I'm so tired.
>> Like what we're learning right now.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. So, that's the dress I got.
>> Stay tuned. Um I'm kind of mad today.
They filled it up a lot. Oh, you better
leave it.
>> Wo. Do you look where you're going?
Because nobody can drive today. I don't
know what's going on.
>> Um I vote this one. Um like a 9 out of
10 today.
Okay, so let's be honest. Did I survive?
What do we think? Yes or no? Let me know
in the comment. No, I survived kind of.
You know, I was
um
I
did everything that I wanted to do in
the week. I woke up on time. I went to
the gym. I drank two of my Stanley's a
day. I got my school work done. I will
say academically that week of school,
probably my worst one yet. But it kind
of wasn't my fault that I had like 15
billion tests in one week.
So, is there a direct correlation with
me waking up early and getting bad
grades? I don't think so. Um, this video
was actually filmed two weeks ago for me
and then the week after the one that I
just went through. I woke up early for
about half of the week and then I got
sick, so I stopped doing that. But the
first half of the week where I was
waking up early, it felt so good. Like I
was already kind of on routine with it
because of this video. So, I will say I
think it is going to be part of my
routine in the morning. Clap y'all.
Clap. Clap for me. That is all. I think
this was a very successful video. I'm
happy that I did it. Now try it for
yourself. Thank you guys so much for
watching. As always, I love you so much.
Have a decent day and goodbye.
[Music]